hanacoric2@gmail.com

HANA CORIC



+45 53 77 36 58

ABOUT ME

I am a 19-year-old multimedia designer studying at Business Academy SouthWest in Esbjerg, Denmark.

Originally from Croatia, since I was little I had a passion for the art of any kind.

I have experience in logo creation, web development, web design, and photo and video production.

After finishing university I aspire to work as a graphic designer or UX/UI designer.

EDUCATION

> HIGH SCHOOL | 2018-2022 |

II. gimnazija Split, Croatia

> HIGHER EDUCATION | 2022-Present |

Business Academy South West Esbjerg, Denmark AP degree in Multimedia Design and Communication

WORK EXPERIENCE

> ETNOGRAPHIC MUSEUM | 2019-2022 |

Split, Croatia
Worked at reception

> HUSET GAMMELHAVN | 2023-Present |

Esbjerg, Denmark Working as a dishwasher

VOLUNTEER WORK

> MULTIPLE SCLEROSIS ASSOCIATION | 2021 |

Helped people with disabilities with everyday situations



LANGUAGE SKILLS

CROATIAN -> I native I ENGLISH -> I advanced I DANISH -> I beginner I

TECHNICAL SKILLS













